A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
You've already done everything you need to do here.
There's no reason for you to stay.
Medusa wants you to join her now to help with some other tasks she has in mind for you.
But I don't want to leave.
I want to stay right here.
Personally, I don't care one way or the other.
I just pass along information.
But I can't say that Medusa will feel the same way.
This is the first time I've ever had friends.
If I leave, I won't be able to see them anymore.
Your whining is giving me a headache.
Just do what Medusa tells you to, idiot.
Sooner or later, everyone here will find out what you did.
Or have you already forgotten the snake you planted in Marie to accelerate the pace of Stein's madness?
When they know about that, there's no way you're going to get off with a reaper chopper, too.
If you know that won't be it.
Just think how Maka will feel.
She'll probably cry.
Don't you see it's over?
Nothing you can do now will change the fact that you betrayed them all.
I'm falling down to my shadow.
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby.
Why do you do this?
I difficult to find any potential.
When you've lost, 13 years
Forever with your soul
見上げれば輝く
月のように
Wake up get out here
We came a long way to get here at least you can do is invite us in and offer us a drink. Are you finished?
That's the Keishin in there you can yell and complain all you want it won't bother him more than a buzzing fly
Well, maybe he'd rather hear the screaming of a mosquito
Looking for a fight old man
Lady Arachne please wait let us go in first
You can stay out there I'll handle this alone
Lady Arachne
Krona's escape show me your smile, please
Greetings Keishin Asherah I am Lady Arachne
I know your great power and respect it. I have journeyed far to meet you
Will you not show me your face?
I've heard others say you hide here because you're timid
But I suspect you came to this isolated mountain to rejuvenate your soul am I correct?
Perhaps I'm wrong
Perhaps you're as afraid of the Grim Reaper as they say
I grow weary of hide-and-seek. Please come out
Go away
Are you this intimidated by a lone woman that's almost cute
I found you?
I've been looking forward to this moment
What are you planning? What is it you want with me woman?
The Reaper has stood in my way long enough
I want you to help me eliminate him
I've hated him for 800 years
I loathe him more now than ever
You understand how that feels? I know you do
If we don't join forces, we'll both fall to him again
Is that what you want?
To be tied up in a sack of your own skin again?
Fight with me
Together we'll be so strong nothing can hurt us
We'll protect each other
I'll give it all to you
Don't you see what I'm offering?
My heart, my soul
All of it is yours to claim
Yummy!
Hey, Krona
You should practice with us the next time we work on Resonance Link
It's fun, and I know you'd add a lot of strength to our team
Oh, uh, yeah
And I'll be there, so you'll be trained by the best of the best
You can't beat that!
Have another sandwich, Krona
There's plenty
Thanks
You may be ugly, but your food is delicious
Actually, I can't take credit for this
This time
It was a special treat from Miss Marie
I'm sure taking care of Professor Stein is pretty hard on her
But somehow she still makes time to take care of us
You're gonna kill whoever did this to the Professor
Of course, I'll have to eat first to build up my strength
Hey, why don't we go visit the Professor?
I'm sure he'd love to see you
What do you say, Krona? Do you want to come along?
I... I... I have to use the restroom
Huh?
You could do that by yourself
I'm staying here
Hey, there's still food to eat
Where are you going?
I want to stay with the food
That's weird even for him
Hmm
It's impossible
How could I ever tell them what I did?
Ragnarok was right, I can't stay
I don't belong here anymore
You're such an obedient child, Krona
You finally see the truth, don't you?
You don't fit in here, not really
The only place you'll ever belong is with me
Lady Medusa
You should be more careful
This belongs in a frame, not on the ground
Oh, yeah
Uh, Maka
Hmm?
Do, um...
Do you think I could ask you something?
Of course
Ask me anything
I, uh...
I was wondering about your mother
Oh, it's complicated
She's sort of missing right now
Wait, hold on
What do you mean missing?
Well, occasionally she'll send me a postcard
So I know she's off somewhere
Traveling around the world
But I don't really know where she is
Or what she's doing
She abandoned her daughter to go on some trip?
Who would do something like that?
So what...
What kind of person is she?
She's like a grizzly bear
A grizzly bear?
She's strong, hot-tempered
You don't want to see her when she's angry
But she's still warm and kind-hearted and loyal
That seems like a lot of things for one person to be
So, um...
Tell me some more
What's the best memory you have from when you were younger...
Of her?
That's easy
Definitely the divorce
Huh?
She was so cool and collected
It was pretty amazing
What a weird answer
Maka's got a strange family life
What's wrong?
Did I say something odd?
Huh?
Oh, no
No!
I know that...
I know she's not around now
But how do you feel about her?
She's my mom, silly
I love her
Huh?
Didn't you say you had to use the restroom?
Yeah
I'll need 500 tons of concrete and 200 tons of I-beams
Also, 30,000 bearings with a 500 millimeter diameter
You think you can make that happen?
Why do you need all that?
Are you planning to build a skyscraper?
Whether it's fixing leaky pipes or constructing a building
If Lord Death asks me to do something, I'll do it
How obedient of you
Hm?
Hey, I forgot to tell you something
If you see Uncle Bob from the coffee shop, I need you to let me know
It's very important, I can't dance without my rumba coffee
I forgot to tell you something, too
You should get some new shoes, sandals aren't safe for construction
Hmm
Does he have no respect for a man's personal taste in footwear?
Joe Buditake
He's a hard man to grasp
Like the steam rising from his coffee cup
I find him unsettling
He reminds me too much of my father
Unwilling to reveal his secrets
Always hiding behind a mask
Not telling anyone what his true intentions are
There, that's much better
What the hell is going on down here?
This is unacceptable
Who can perpetrate such a horror?
And there he goes, we've lost him again
Hey, wait!
Where did he go?
Let it panic!
This kid is becoming troublesome
Why is he so persistent?
He should just relax with a good cup of coffee
It was like this when I got here
Empty
No belongings
No crona
He probably ran away
Why would he do that?
He's been acting strange lately
Don't tell me you haven't noticed
Distant, scared all the time
It almost seemed like he didn't want to hang around with us anymore
Admit it
You sensed it too
At any rate, Lord Death will find out he's gone sooner or later
And he won't be pleased
I'll find him
Hey, Mokka?
Just like her
Running off after him without a thought in her head
Rona, why?
Why'd you go?
Where are you?
Why now?
I don't understand
Everyone thinks you ran away, but they're wrong
Aren't they?
I don't know why you're so bummed
Just think
We never have to look at their ugly faces again
Give it a little while
Once you get home
You'll forget all about the stupid academy
I don't think so
I'm not going back to Medusa
Huh?
I can't stay at the academy
And I can't go home
I just want to be alone
A weakling like you
You won't last two days on your own
What are you gonna do for food?
If you're not going to Medusa's
You might as well turn around and go back to the academy
Get off of me!
There's no way I can go back there!
Stupid kid
What are you doing trying to starve me?
I couldn't stand them being so nice to me after I betrayed them
It was breaking my heart
You don't know anything you useless panty!
Stop it!
That hurts!
Get off of me!
Please forgive me Lady Aragne
You must be in so much pain
That should never have happened while I was with you
It's all my fault
Please
Please forgive me
We succeeded in recruiting the Kishin to our side
This is a time to celebrate, not to cry
Yes
My lady
Well, it wasn't easy, but I did it.
Our new Kishan friend's been given the best bedroom we had available.
He even had a little snack on the way.
Three of our men.
He's like a dog being introduced to its new owner for the first time.
He'll be suspicious of us at first.
Tasty.
How long are we gonna stay in this hole?
I'm baking in the sun!
I found a place where I can be alone like I wanted.
I'll stay here until I'm ready to leave.
Oh, so hot. I can't take it.
My insides are starting to boil!
I've been somewhere like this before.
A lonely place without water.
That's where we met.
My first lonely place in the desert.
Will you let me be your friend, Krona?
It was like feeling sunlight for the first time.
But we were as different as night and day.
How could I ever let myself imagine our friendship would last?
It was a nice dream, I guess.
But it would be better if I could forget it.
Krona!
You're sure this is the right spot?
Yeah.
I'm positive I can feel a soul nearby.
Krona!
Maka.
Stop here, soul.
Krona!
I finally found you and let's get you out of there.
Hey, soul!
Give me a hand!
Why did you come after me?
You can leave me alone.
I didn't ask for your help.
Go away.
I said go away!
Why, Krona?
I don't want you here.
You don't understand anything about me.
Go!
Just get out of here!
I can't look at you.
Not after what I did.
The things that have been happening to Professor Stein.
Those are all because of me.
It was in Miss Marie's drink.
I put one of Lady Medusa's special little snakes in it.
Miss Marie never even suspected me for a second.
She liked me.
She kept telling me what a good kid I was.
Why'd she do that?
I never asked her to be nice to me.
Having faith in other people?
Trusting someone not to hurt you?
How idiotic is that?
You know?
Stop.
Don't move.
Not another word.
Maka.
Hey!
Don't you dare say one more negative thing about yourself.
You think of yourself as someone who's cowardly and weak.
Yet whenever something happens, you put everyone else first.
And then...
You end up getting hurt.
Please stop this.
You're hurting my friend and I can't take it.
It was Medusa who made you do it.
You didn't want to, did you?
Well?
Please tell me I'm right.
No.
I can't say it.
Don't, don't you see?
She's my mother.
I hate this so much.
But there's nothing I can do.
I'm so tired of all this.
When can I stop hurting people.
I don't want to hurt anybody.
I don't want to make people sad.
I don't want to lose my only friend.
You see?
I am a coward, like I said.
And, and I might end up betraying you again.
I won't let that happen.
I promise I won't.
What do you say?
Can we go home?
Have they realized they're in a big hole yet?
I suppose they're expecting me to dig them out of there.
Not cool.
Not even a little bit cool.
I understand your loyalty to your friend.
But Krona did sign the Academy Agreement.
Students who break the rules are expelled.
That's the way it works.
Making an exception for him
would undermine the stability of the entire Academy.
It can't be done.
Krona knows he was wrong.
He already apologized for what he did.
He feels awful about all of it.
Maka.
This problem can't be solved by saying sorry.
What Krona did was extremely serious.
You're a fine one to talk about loyalty.
Huh?
You don't know what loyalty is.
How many promises did you break
when you and Mom were together?
How many times did you say sorry
only to do it again?
Those two situations have nothing in common.
Don't you understand the gravity of this?
No, I don't.
If you got a second chance, so should he.
I trust him not to do it again.
Lord Death.
Huh?
An urgent police report.
Someone's been sighted in the city.
Someone being...
The Snake Woman has come back.
It's Medusa.
Why have you come here?
I'm not here to fight you.
I surrender.
Yeah
oh
you
Oh wow, that was a really good episode, wasn't it sis?
I guess, if you're sentimental
That part at the end was so sweet, it made me cry
I suppose it was a little touching
It looks like it even made you cry, big sis
I'm not crying, I don't know what you're talking about
But your face is wet and your eyes are all puffy
On the next episode of Soul Eater, the cards are cut, Medusa surrenders to the DWMA
I told you, I wasn't crying